<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Interview</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>

    <string name="home_second">Home Second</string>
    <string name="cs_and_it">Interview question for CS \ IT</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips for preparation to interview</string>
    <string name="key_project_description">This is profile web-site of a color promotion company, which is advertising company, they advertise through mobile van, digital wall painting, audio recording, the role in this project as frontend design and this is live web-site, colourspromotion.com.</string>
    <string name="internship_experience">It was a Five week internship program where I was trained in Android and henceforth given a project of their requirement to be completed within deadline in Android Studio. On their requirement we make prototype using Adobe XD and build project as Bulk SMS and Mail Application in Android Studio, this application is built in such a way that it is able to send bulk messages at a time to the clients ,Not only messages but we can also send bulk emails at a time with help of our Premium SMS services provided by Ascellent technologies. </string>
    <string name="text">Declaration of a variable/function simply declares that the variable/function exists somewhere in the program but the memory is not allocated for them. But the declaration of a variable/function serves an important role. And that is the type of the variable/function.__bTherefore, when a variable is declared, the program knows the data type of that variable. In case of function declaration, the program knows what are the arguments to that functions, their data types, the order of arguments and the return type of the function.__bSo that’s all about declaration. Coming to the definition, when we define a variable/function, apart from the role of declaration, it also allocates memory for that variable/function. Therefore, we can think of definition as a super set of declaration. (or declaration as a subset of definition).</string>

</resources>
